Do you know
how many years of insurance you get with your bike? If
you know that you get 5 years, then
how is it, you will know after watching this entire video.
Hello friends, my name
is Vinod Kumar and welcome to your face again.
In today's video, I am going to
tell you that you have bought a new bike.
How many years of insurance do you get with a new bike?
You guys are
told about 5 years of insurance at that time. So
today I am going to tell you completely whether it is for
5 years or less
or what is the
complete rule of insurance. So I am going to tell you everything.
Watch the video till the end and
watch the entire video, only then you will understand what is
this insurance system, how is 5 years
insurance and what all is there in it. So you will
know in some videos. Let's
start then and my name is Vinod Kumar
and welcome to your own Adventure Britain. So
let's start.
So whenever you buy a bike, you will know that along with
that you have to
take an insurance policy. The work of an insurance policy is
that your  If your bike is ever stolen,
damaged, or meets with an
accident, you
get a lot of cover in that, which is
money you get and
some percentage for repairing your bike is given to
you by the company with which you have insured it,
and something similar happens in case of theft, so this is what happens
in insurance, and
when you buy a new bike, you
get 5 years insurance on it, this
was implemented in 2020, earlier you
could get a normal 1 year policy, but it has become
personally compulsory, so you should understand
how you get 5 years insurance,
so let me tell you, first of all
you are given an insurance of Rs 500 along with the bike
and along with that, the payment for 5 years
insurance is also taken at the same time
and 5 years insurance is
given to you, but if you ever buy a new bike, then
definitely read its insurance, it is
written in it that it is one party insurance, it is
first party insurance and the rest is for
14 years and there is third party
insurance, so this  I have found out everything by
reading my insurance. I will
also give you the details of my insurance here on the
side, you can see that too. It is
clearly written in it that one year
means first party and the remaining
four years are going to be third party,
so how will the insurance work in this,
first party means that for one year,
whatever damage happens to your bike completely bumper-to-bumper,
that means you are going to get the full money, the
company is going to bear the entire damage cost
and if after one year, if your bike gets
damaged and your bike has third
party insurance, then you are
not going to get anything for any damage in it, so there is some system for this that if
you mean if you want to get your bike, whatever the
word means, whether it is
boosted again or whatever is stolen,
cleaned, then for that you should have
minimum first party insurance, so
your one year will be complete, then
after that you will have to renew the
insurance again, otherwise you
can avoid third party verification and you can avoid Zafar and police and
you are getting relief only from challan,
talk to that  Any
damage, any accident, any theft, there is no
clarity on it, so the
company will give you one year, the rest they
say for five years and the
rest is for four years, which absolutely
means that it is third party and
you will not get any claim on third party,
you will have to renew it every year,
so in this I
am giving you a chart next to it, you understand in it that if
you have got your bike insured for two years, then
how much percentage will you get on it, if
your bike gets damaged, you take PM, I am
showing you the chart on Google, you
can understand it again, and I have
told you this in simple and clear words
that bike insurance is only for one year
first party, the remaining four years are
third party and
you can ask these companies, I also
asked them on my friend list, then
they told me that in a conspiracy, the
first party and the remaining four years are third party,
you will have to renew, so
when you go to buy a bike, do ask this thing,
and even after asking, you will
get this insurance  Because the
insurance that comes from the company is the same, so that
you will have to renew it every year according to your
bike,
it is going to be renewed according to your bike rally, so
how did you like today's video, in this I have
given some special information related to insurance, which will make you understand that there should
not be any problem in cleaning your bike
in future, so you guys should also
watch this video completely and after watching and withdrawing, if you liked the
video then like it and will
ask the channel, all the videos keep coming here
and press the bell icon also and some people
think that if they subscribe to the channel then it
means they will have to pay or something like that, it
is absolutely free on YouTube,
you guys can subscribe to all this, they are not
fooled by those asking for balance, it is free of
cost, absolutely, so subscribe to the channel
and like the video, we will meet
you in the next video, till then say bye
-bye